https://www.aad.org/legal-notice

AAD
Welcome!
Featured
Make it easy for patients to find you.
Update your Find a Dermatologist profile, the Academy's directory that's visited by over 1 million people a year.
Meet the new AAD
Learn about the Academy's efforts to refocus its brand on education, advocacy, member-centricity, and innovation.
Featured
AAD Virtual Meeting Experience (VMX)
AAD VMX includes 14 robust sessions covering topics such as therapeutics, cosmetics, psoriasis, hair disorders, and more.
Education Center
Discover the wealth of educational opportunities offered through the Academy.
Prior authorization letter tool
What is a prior authorization?
Telederm toolkit
Health information tech (HIT)
Featured
Need coding help?
Find practical guidance on coding issues common in dermatology practices.
MIPS: Step-by-step guide
Learn how to avoid a penalty and earn an incentive when reporting MIPS for 2019.
Clinical guidelines
Review current clinical guidelines, those in development, and guidelines that the AAD has collaborated on.
Why use AAD measures?
The Academy has developed 22 quality measures to help advance quality improvement.
Latest news
Read this month's top stories in Dermatology World.
New insights
Check out DermWorld Insights & Inquiries for the latest updates from Dr. Warren Heymann
Combat burnout
Access tools and practical guidance in evaluating and overcoming personal and staff burnout.
Joining or selling a practice?
Get help to evaluate what practice model fits your needs, as well as guidance on selling a practice.
Advocacy priorities
Learn about the Academy's advocacy priorities and how to join efforts to protect your practice.
Promote the specialty
Access resources to help you promote the specialty in your community and beyond.
Legal notice
Privacy policyThe American Academy of Dermatology (the Academy) is committed to maintaining the privacy of the personally identifiable information of visitors to its sites. Our policies are designed to disclose the information collected and how it will be used. This policy applies solely to the information provided while visiting this website. The terms of the privacy policy do not govern personal information furnished through any means other than this website (such as by telephone, mail, or email).Personal informationPersonal information such as postal and email address may be used internally for maintaining member records, and for marketing purposes for the AAD and AAD partners alerting customers or members of additional services available. Phone numbers may also be used by the Academy when questions about products or services arise. Aggregated or other non-personal information may be shared (i.e. information about you and other customers collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you) with third parties. We may also share this information, as well as persistent cookies (as defined below), with third parties to develop and deliver targeted advertising to you on our websites and retargeted advertising to you when you visit websites of third parties. We also may share aggregated information with third parties, including advertisers, research companies, vendors, and affinity partners for the purpose of conducting general business analysis. For example, we may tell our advertisers the number of visitors to our website and the most popular features or services accessed. This information does not contain any personal information and may be used to develop website content and services that we hope you and other users will find of interest and to more appropriately target content and advertising. If you are an individual located within the European Union (EU), your personal data will be processed, used and stored in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Click here for our complete GDPR Privacy Policy.CookiesThis website uses pixels, which are a type of code that triggers user cookies. A cookie is a small file stored on the site user's computer or Web server. Session cookies are temporary files created when a user signs in on the website or uses the personalized features (such as keeping track of items in the shopping cart). Session cookies are removed when a user logs off or when the browser is closed. Persistent cookies are permanent files and must be deleted manually through the site user’s web browser. Tracking or other information collected from persistent cookies or any session cookie is used to provide users with efficient navigation of the site, for the collection of site use analytics, or for marketing purposes, including retargeted marketing when users of this website visit the websites of third parties.Information provided on a form (such as registering for the Annual Scientific Meeting) is maintained at the Academy solely for that intended use, unless stated otherwise.Third Party CookiesPlease note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.
Advertisement
Advertisement
Advertisement
